Don't go down without a fight.
Elevation is a action, science fiction, thriller film directed by George Nolfi.
Post-apocalyptic survivors find refuge in the Rocky Mountains to hide from
giant, insect-like creatures that can't live above 8,000 feet.
However, when one of them needs life-saving supplies, they
risk it all to venture into the danger zone.
Will, played by Anthony Mackie.
Nina, played by Morena Baccarin.
Katie, played by Maddie Hasson.
Hunter, played by Danny Boyd Jr..
Tara, played by Rachel Nicks.
Hannah, played by Shauna Earp.
Elevation is a 2024 American post-apocalyptic action thriller film directed
by George Nolfi and written by Kenny Ryan and Jacob Roman.
It stars Anthony Mackie, Morena Baccarin, and Maddie Hasson.
Elevation was released in the United States on November 8, 2024.
The film explores themes of mine, colorado, alien, hospital, alien invasion.
The tone is thought_provoking and intense.